Hello, I'm Miyu Matsuo.
I've been asked to make a video about the behind-the-scenes of Under Live, our 33rd single.
There are some videos that were taken by the managers and the members.
I think there are a lot of people in this video that you can't usually see!
So please take a look!
We worked hard for 3 days!
Thank you very much!
Ending
Can I have this?
Can I have it?
I can bring it tomorrow.
What are today's socks from Mikia?
They're cute.
You love them?
Yes, they're cute.
They're cute.
I bought them when I was in Ehime.
Ehime?
You went to Ehime?
Grandpa.
He's so cute.
So cute.
Are you okay?
So, uh-uh.
Oh, God, I'm scared.
I'm scared. I'm scared. He's gonna rip my shoulder off.
I'm scared. I'm scared.Scary.
I'm going to rip it off, before the show
Shoulder ripped off
Thank you for watching.
Joehiru nome wurden
eat
I see it's different this way.
And I'm 12 years old.
What?
I thought I was 12.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why does it look good on you?
It's just that it doesn't look good on me right now.
It looks good on you.
You look like you'd wear it for casual wear.
What's that?
I don't know.
That's amazing.
I think Vinzers looks good on me.
Let's bump it up.
Sure thing.
Thank you for watching.
Evolve.
Eventually forgetting the past
And live for tomorrow
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watchingThank you for watching!
I'm nervous.
Who's here to watch? Mothers.
A lot of my friends are here.
A lot of your friends are here?
Ayako and...
It happened to be the last day of school.
Oh, wow.
I'm so nervous.
Let's make sure it's a success.
As expected...
As expected.
I'm going to go change.
I'm off!
You're so cute.
Are you nervous today?
No, I'm not.
Oh, my God.
On the contrary, I'm a little less nervous now.
On the contrary.
You're a genius.
Fighting.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for your hard work.
Here's a YouTube testimonial.
That's a lot.
I've never seen the taping look darker the other way around.
That's for sure.Indeed.
It's proof that you jumped a lot.
I wish I could.
Have you used any cosmetics?
I think I'm ready for a vaccine now.
I've never thought about it.
Yes, I have.
It's so heavy.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's showing
Let's go for it
I'm off!
Think about it calmly.
We've danced a crazy number of dances.
I've done a lot of rehearsals.
I'm sure it all means I'm comfortable with my body
I danced comfortably
So, I think
I think it's all in the end.
Let's enjoy it!
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Today is the third single of Nogizaka46
Thank you very much for coming to "Under Live" today.
Thank you very much.
I'm Kaede Sato.
I am Inoha Okada.
I'm Arie Shimizu.
Did you miss us today?Did you guys miss us today?
Are you guys ready to step on the sidewalk?
Last day!
Let's go for it!
I'm hungry.
I'm starving!
Close, close, close.
How close was it?
It's right here.
It's out of focus.
It doesn't work.
Are you sure this is the right mission?
Mission? It's the best.
Only Mitterrand's senior could do this.
That's not true.
But it's great.
Thank you very much.
Brought you guys some goodies.
Wow, you took two three-leggeds?
You'll probably get caught.
Yes, thieves.
In bananas.
The lettering thieves.
The lettering thief is amazing.
There's pumpkins, too.
I like the mushrooms.
But I'm sure I'll spill it!But I'm definitely going to spill that one.
We'd better dig it up.
You'd better go after it.
spill it or drop it.
That's for sure.
Already on the line!
How was everyone's close-up video?
Seeno!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Bye bye!